(Sheldon:)unlikely to ever reach
(Sheldon:)the nourishing teats
of Indiana Jones.
(Leonard:)So I guess it's a good thing
we stopped for dinner.
(Raj:)You know, guys, when
facing disappointment,
Eat, Pray, Love  teaches us--
(Howard:)Oh, shut up.
(Amy:)...so anyway, to make
a long story short,
(Amy:)turns out I have
an unusually firm cervix.
(Leonard:)You--
Amy, when we say "girl talk,"
(Penny:)it doesn't just have to
be about our lady parts.
Shame. 'Cause I have a real
zinger about my titled uterus.
(Bernadette:)Penny, your nails
look great.
(Penny:)Oh, thanks. I found
this place in Alhambra.
(Penny:)It's in a woman's basement.
(Penny:)I think it's a front
for human trafficking,
but they do a really good job.